# RAGHAVI C S

EDUCATOR, TECHNICAL WRITER, WEB CONTENT WRITER, SEO SPECIALIST, ACADEMIC WRITER, PROOF READING, CONTENT EDITOR, COPY EDITOR, BLOG WRITER, TRAVEL WRITER

- +91 8147024908
- 🗷 ckmraghavi@gmail.com
- LinkedIn
- Ohikmagalur, Karnataka 577101

## **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Education [Physics/Mathematics]

University of Mysore CGPA - 9.44, 2020 - 2022

## Master's in Physics

University of Mysore CGPA - 8.4, 2018 - 2020

## B.Sc [Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics]

University of Mysore 79.65%, 2015 - 2018

#### PU [PCMB]

Department of Pre-university Education, Karnataka 89.83%, 2013 - 2015

### SSLC

KSEEB, Karnataka 90.88%, 2013

#### **AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Awarded as "TOPPER OF THE BATCH" during B.Ed course.
- Qualified both papers of CTET (P1 99M, P2-108M)
- Qualified KARTET (P2 92M)
- Achieved an AIR 11 in the M. Tech (Nanotechnology) exam conducted by Central University of Tamilnadu.
- Awarded as "BEST EVENT COORDINATOR" of the year 2018 – 2019 during M.Sc
- Awarded as "BEST LEADER" in Community Living Camp held at Ramanahalli, Mysuru (19th-23rd April 2022) during B.Ed course.
- Awarded as "STAR PLAYER OF THE YEAR" 2021 2022 during B.Ed course.

# **LANGUAGE**

## **ABOUT ME**

As an accomplished teacher and content writer, my strength lies in effective communication, adapting teaching to diverse needs of people. Collaboration is a corner stone of my approach, proficient in assessment design, constructive feedback on pupil growth, technological integration and enhancing knowledge experience.

## **EXPERTISE**

MS WORD, MS EXCEL, MS POWERPOINT, Canva, Linux, Kawoot, Wordpress, Supremeseo, Microniche, Grammarly, Plagarism Checker, Microsoft Bing, SEO, Graphic Designing, Digital marketing

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

O Dec 2022 - Present

Vidhyaashram Institutions | Mysuru, Karnataka

### Science Educator

To inspire, motivate, educate young learners, making instruction strategies, creating activities that brings out the overall development of learners, creating a playful atmosphere to teach interdisciplinary subjects.

2020 - 2023

Lambdageeks | Bangalore, Karnataka

#### **Content Writer**

Researching subject related topics, combining online sources, writing a market copy to promote the depth knowledge of technologies, preparing SEO optimized drafts using content management systems.

#### RESEARCH & PUBLICATIONS

Published a Paper on the topic "Using the Approach of Atal Tinkering Lab to Enhance Scientific Thinking to Realize NEP 2020 Vision for Young Learners" in the field of Multidisciplinary and Holistic Approach during the International seminar organised by SJCE college, Mysuru.

Published nearly **700 SEO optimized articles** on the topics such as solar panels, renewable resources, physics, animal queries, heat pumps, heaters, air conditioners that stands among top 10 rankings on the google.

## REFERENCES

# Dr. Priya Mathew

Principal / SJCE, Mysuru

Phone: +91 9482538060

Email: priyamathew@gmail.com

# Mrs. Shalom Sannutha

Asst.Professor/SJCE, Mysuru

Phone: +91 620251977

Email: sunmonila30@gmail.com